<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<new>
<reccomandation>
<name>Six Senses Douro Valley</name>
<location>Portugal, Lamego</location>
<time>LOCAL TIME 10:07 PM </time>
<description>
This beautifully renovated and reimagined 19th-century manor house is set high
 on a hill overlooking the vine-covered countryside of the Douro Valley and the
  river below. From the dreamily-designed and furnished rooms and suites 
to the expansive spa, fine and wholesome wining and dining, organic gardens 
and nature trails, this is where well-being meets pure joy.
</description>
<redirect XML-LINK="LINK" HREF="https://www.sixsenses.com/en/resorts/douro-valley">More about us</redirect>
</reccomandation>

<reccomandation>
<name>Six Senses Zighy Bay</name>
<location>Oman, Musandam Peninsula</location>
<time>LOCAL TIME 1:08 AM</time>
<description>Nestled in Oman’s dramatic Musandam Peninsula, where rugged mountains dive into vibrant
 emerald waters, across a powdery sand beach, the village-inspired resort offers a range of villas,
  suites and beachfront retreats, each with a private pool, traditional summer house and the time 
  and space to find yourself. There’s something for everyone including 
eclectic dining featuring local and international cuisine, an award-winning spa and a plethora of unique experiences.</description>

<redirect XML-LINK="LINK" HREF="https://www.sixsenses.com/en/resorts/zighy-bay">More about us</redirect>
</reccomandation>

<reccomandation>
<name>Six Senses Fiji</name>
<location>Fiji, Malolo Island</location>
<time>LOCAL TIME 9:10 AM </time>
<description>Sublime Malolo Island is the tropical setting for Six Senses Fiji, only 16 miles (25 kilometers) 
from Nadi International Airport (NAN). Surrounded by crystal clear waters
 and white sand beaches, the resort features just 24 spacious pool villas plus an inventory 
 of residences with two to five bedrooms.</description>
<redirect XML-LINK="LINK" HREF="https://www.sixsenses.com/en/resorts/fiji">More about us</redirect>
</reccomandation>
</new>